Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Student Manager, Series 3
  - Student Manager's Report, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Associated students; bonfire report; Chaparral audit; circular letter; circle "S" society boxing; contracts; concert series; convalescent home; cotillion; debate report; Encina Club; Irish marathon; junior prom; Labor Day; masque ball; men's glee club; memorandum; military ball; publications; registration dances; sigma delta chi; senior class gift; senior ball; Toyon club; women
  - Student Manager's Report, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Associated students; bonfire report; boxing tournament; Branner club dances; building and loan letter; Chaparral; circular letter; concert series; cotillion; convalescent home; debate; Encina club; English club; fees; junior prom; Labor Day; men's glee club; military ball; pavilion letter; publications; quad; registration dances; senior class; Toyon club; University orchestra; vocational guidance; women's athletic association; women's gymnasium fund
  - Student Manager's Report, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Associated students; bonfire report; Branner club dances; concert series; convalescent home; cotillion; Encina dances; engineer's dance; junior water carnival; junior prom; masque ball; men's glee club; men's debate; registration dances; Roble club; senior class; scalper's charter; Toyon; union fees; women's athletic association
  - Student Manager's Report, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Associated students; bonfire; Branner club; concert series; convalescent home; sophomore cotillion; Encina club; English club; handbook contract; junior week; men's debate; masque ball; men's glee club; military ball; registration dances; rugby contest; Roble club; seniors; terms for scholarships; Toyon; publications; Stanford bookstore; student's relief dance; W.A.A.
  - Student Manager's Report, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Associated students; circle "S" boxing; concert series; convalescent home; class of 1937; sophomore cotillion; Encina club; registration dances; Toyon; junior week; interhall informal; masque ball; men's debate; men's rushing; military ball; phi phi; Roble club; registration dances; seniors; W.A.A.; publications
  - Student Manager's Report, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Associated students; concert series; convalescent home; Encina club; English club; interfraternity council; junior week; men's debate; military ball; masque ball; music fund; Roble club; registration dances; sophomore cotillion; senior class; Stanford dividex; Toyon club; magazines; union club; W.A.A.; YWCA; publications
  - Student Manager's Report, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Associated students; barnstormers; Branner club; cardinals; conference party; concert series; convalescent home; debate council; Encina club; English club; juniors; Lagunita Court; masque ball; men's glee club; military ball; pledge dance; Roble club; sophomores; senior class; speakers bureau; theatre letter; W.A.A.; YMCA; publications
  - Student Manager's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Associated students; associated women students; Branner club; cardinals; circle "S"; concert series; convalescent home; debate; Encina club; flying club; handbook contract; interfraternity; junior prom; Lagunita dances; Madrono note; masque ball; men's glee club; military ball; phi phi dances; pi delta phi; pre registration; registration dances; Roble club; sophomores; senior class; speakers bureau; Stanford young democrats; union club; vocational guidance; WAA; YWCA; publications; Wilbur letters
  - Student Manager's Report, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Associated students; associated women students; Branner club; big game; cap and gown; cardinals; circle "S" boxing; class of 1939; class of 1940; concert series; cotillion; convalescent home; Encina club; interfraternity; juniors; Lagunita club; married men; masque ball; men's debate; men's glee club; pre registration program; phi phi; pi delta phi; pledge prom; registration dances; Roble club; senior class; sophomore class; ski club; Stanford dividex; political union; Toyon club; union club; WAA; publications
  - Student Manager's Report, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Associated students; associated women students; axe society; boat house day; charters; constitutional changes; debate council; international committee; lecture series; motion picture; peace day; really committee; red cross; speakers bureau; Branner club; cardinals; Cal-Stanford frosh; concert series; convalescent home; encina club; handbook; interfraternity pledge; junior class; Lagunita club; masque ball; men's glee club; military ball; phi phi; pre registration program; registration dances; Roble club; senior class; sophomore cotillion; Toyon club; union club; WAA; women's glee club
  - Student Manager's Report, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Associated students; associated women students; activities; axe society; alpha phi omega; back to the farm; big game; Branner club; business school; cardinals; Cal-Stanford frosh; circle "s" boxing; concert series; convalescent home; debate; Encina club; handbook; interclub dance; interfraternity; junior prom; junior water carnival; transfer orientation; Lagunita club; leadership institute; lecture series; peace day; phi phi dance; pre-registration; rally committee; red cross; registration dances; Roble club; sophomores; senior class; speakers bureau; Stanford glee club; theta sigma phi; Toyon club; union club; WAA; weekly informer; YMCA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Associated students; associated women students; cardinals; convalescent home; co-op bookstore; concert series; debate; Encina club; pre-registration; Roble; rally committee; sophomores; senior class; Stanford's history; YMCA; WAW
  - Student Manager's Report, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Associated students; activities; associated women's students; bond drive; boxing tournament; Branner club; brunch; Cal-Stanford frosh; Cardinals; concert series; convalescent home; co-op books; drama council; debating; Encina club; freshman picture book; handbook; interfraternity council; junior class; Lagunita club; lecture series; movies; panhellenic red cross; pre-registration; red cross; registration dances; Roble club; sophomores; junior class; senior class; Toyon club; union club; WAA; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Associated students; associated women students; Branner; cap and gown; cardinals; concert series; co-op books; convalescent home; debate; drama council; drives committee; Encina club; flying indian unit; freshman formal; junior prom; Lagunita formal; pre-registration; rally committee; red cross; Roble; senior program; sophomore carnival; student army dance; Toyon; war board; world student serivce fund; YWCA; union-Lagunita formal
  - Student Manager's Report, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Associated students; army-student letter; axe history; associated women students; barbecue; cardinal minutes; class activities; convalescent home; concert series; debate; dramatic council; emergency plans; movies; pan american fiesta; pre-registration; rallies; recreation conference; registration dances; red cross drive; Roble club; social policy; soldier dances; spring sing; Tyler hall; YWCA; war board; war fund; WAA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Associated students; AWS; cardinals; convalescent home; Branner women's club; class of 1948; class of 1947; class of 1946; class of 1945; concert series; debate council; dramatic council; handbook; international club; lagunita club; movies; music council; olympic day; pre-registration; registration dances; Roble club; Roble-Branner-Ventura dances; Sequoia club; student relations; Toyon freshman club; Toyon summer club; Tyler hall; vocational guidance; war board; WAA; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Associated students; associated women students; cardinals; convalescent home; Branner club; Buchanan hall; christian science organization; class of 1946; class of 1947; class of 1948; class of 1949; concert series; dramatic council; Encina club; honor code committee; lagunita club; men's glee club; olympic club; Sunday evening movie; student firemen; rally committee; pre-registration; registration dances; Roble club; Tyler hall; war board; WAA; world student service fund; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    President's report; vice-president's report; student manager's report and correspondence; inventories; ASSU; AWS; ASSU cardinals; ASSU convalescent home drive; ASSU debate council; ASSU election board; ASSU handbook; ASSU honor code standing committee; ASSU movies; ASSU music council; ASSU pre reg program; ASSU rally committee; ASSU relief fund drive; american veterans' committee; badminton club; Branner club; Class of 1947; Class of 1948; Class of 1949; Class of 1950; concert series; dramatic council; Encina club; geology and mining society; graduate school of business; graduate women; hawaiian club; institute of international relations; international club; lagunita; NSA; reg dances; Roble club; row excomm; Stanford flying club; Stanford law school; Stanford village; Toyon club; union club; union residence club; village clubs; WAA; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report 1947-1948 Vol I, A-C (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Associated students; ASSU summer quarter; activities agency; elections; handbook; honor code; men's housing; pre-reg; AWS; cardinals; debate; rally committee; Branner women's club; class of 1948; class of 1949; class of 1950; class of 1951; concert series; co-recreation committee
  - Student Manager's Report 1947-1948 Vol II, C-Z (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Drama council; Encina club; graduate school of business; graduate women; institute of international relations; international club; interfraternity council; lagunita club; men's glee club; movies; NSA; quarterdeck society; registration dances; Roble club; row ex com; Stanford crew; Stanford law association; Stanford relief fund; Stanford ski club; Stanford village; Toyon club; union club; casa ventura; WAA
  - Student Manager's Report 1948-1949 Vol I, A-B (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Associated students; AWS; cardinals; debate council; elections; foreign scholarship; rally committee; ASCE; Branner women's club
  - Student Manager's Report 1948-1949 Vol II, C-Z (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Class of 1949; class of 1950; class of 1951; class of 1952; concert series; co-rec folk dance festival; Encina club; graduate school of business; institute of international relations; international club; interfraternity council; lagunita club; men's glee club; movies; NSA; quarterdeck society; ram's head productions; registration dances; Roble club; row ex com; scabbard and blade; Stanford chinese dance; Stanford hot jazz society; Stanford law ass'n; Stanford relief fund; Stanford ski club; village council; Toyon club; union club; union planning committee; WAA
  - Student Manager's Report 1949-1950 Vol I, A-B (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Associated students; AWS; cardinals; debate; election chairman's report; foreign scholarship; rally committee; Branner women's club
  - Student Manager's Report 1949-1950 Vol II, C-Z (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Class of 1950; class of 1951; class of 1952; class of 1953; co-recreation committee; Encina club; frosh-soph jamboree; graduate school of business; housing committee; IIR; intercollegiate charity show; lagunita club; leadership conference; men's glee club; movies; NSA; Ram's Head productions; Roble club; registration dances; row ex com; scabbard and blade; Stanford chinese club; Stanford crew; Stanford flying club; Stanford law association; Stanford relief fund drive; Stanford ski club movie; Stanford tennis club; Stanford village; Stern club; Storey club; Toyon club; union club; union planning; WAA; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report 1950-1951 Vol I, A (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Associated Students: President's report; vice-president's report; student managers' reports; AWS; cardinals; debate board; election board; foreign scholarship; men's council; public relations; rally committee; summer quarter; student-faculty educational commission
  - Student Manager's Report 1950-1951 Vol II, B-Z (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Branner club; casa ventura; class of 1951; class of 1952; class of 1953; class of 1954; concert series; co-recreation committee; graduate school of business; IIR; interfraternity council; informer; lagunita club; leadership conference; men's glee club; movies; quarterback society; ram's head production; registration dances; Roble club; Roth club; row ex-com; Stanford chinese club; Stanford law association; Stanford relief fund drive; Stern club; Storey club; Toyon club; union club; village council; village film society; women's residence summer club; WAA; YWCA
  - Student Manager's Report 1951-1952 Vol I, A (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Associated Students: President's report; summer quarter president's report; vice-president's report; student managers' reports; AWS; cardinals; debate board; election board; foreign scholarship board; committees; student workshop; men's council; Sunday evening movies; public relations; rally committee; student-faculty education committee
  - Student Manager's Report 1951-1952 Vol II, B-Z (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Branner club; boathouse; casa ventura; class of 1952; class of 1953; class of 1954; class of 1955; concert series; co-recreation association; Crothers club; delta theta phi; Durand club; Encina; frosh-soph jamboree; graduate school of business; geological and mining society; IRR; lagunita club; leadership conference; maison francaise; Newman club barbecue; pajamarino; Ram's Head productions; registration dances; Roble club; Roth club; row carnival; row dance; sigma delta pi; Stanford law association dance; Stanford relief fund drive; Stanford ski club; Stern club; Storey club; Stanford village; Toyon club; union club; women's residence summer club; WAA
  - Student Manager's Report 1952-1953 Vol I, A (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Associated students; alpha phi omega; AWS; cardinals; debate; election board; foreign scholarship; frosh handbook; leadership conference; pre-registration; public relations; political committee; rally committee; summer quarter
  - Student Manager's Report 1952-1953 Vol II, B-Z (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Block s society; Branner women's club; chinese students club; Class of 1953; class of 1954; class of 1955; class of 1956; concert series; co-recreation association; Durand club; frosh-soph jamboree; graduate school of business club; Hurlburt club; IIR, interclub council; lagunita club; Lathrop club; military ball; Sunday evening movies; Newman club; off-campus men's organization; police; Ram's Head productions; registration dances; Roble club; women's row; Stanford alpine club; Stanford crew; Stanford relief fund drive; Stanford ski club; Stanford soccer association; Stanford sports car club; Stanford law association; Stanford village; Storey club; Stern club; Toyon club; union club; union residence club; WAA; WRSC
  - Student Manager's Report 1953-1954 Vol I, ASSU (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Report of the student body president: Donald D. Lozabnick
  - Student Manager's Report 1953-1954 Vol II, ASSU (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Axe society; beaux arts ball; Branner women's club; casa ventura; chinese students; class of 1954; class of 1955; class of 1956; class of 1957; concert series; co-recreation committee; Crothers club; delta phi epsilon; Durand club; elm cottage; Encina club; frosh-soph jamboree; graduate school of business; graduate student association; hawaiian club; Hurlburt club; IIR; interclub council; inter fraternity magazine; lagunita club; Lathrop club; manzanita club; mariposa club; military ball; movies; Newman club; oaks club; off campus women; phi delta phi; Ram's Head productions; registration dances; Roble club; row ex com; Russell club; Stanford relief fund drive; Stanford village; Stern club; Storey club; Stanford law school; Stanford ski club; Toyon club; union club; union residence; women's residences summer club
  - Student Manager's Report 1954-1955 Vol I, A-B (Box 10, Folder 1)
    AFROTC; ASME; Associated students; AWS; cardinals; concert series; election board; foreign scholarship; frosh handbook; IIR; movies; NSA; political union; pre-registration; public relations board; rally committee; speech activities; student-faculty; yell leaders; block and circle "s" society; Branner women's club; casa ventura; ASSU movies
  - Student Manager's Report 1954-1955 Vol II, C-Z (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Class of 1955; class of 1956; class of 1957; class of 1958; Crothers club; delta phi epsilon; Durand club; education club; Encina club; frosh-soph jamboree; geology and mining society; graduate school of business; graduate student association; interclub council; interfraternity council; Jordan club; lagunita club; Lathrop club; military ball; Newman club; quarterdeck society; Ram's Head productions; registration dances; Roble club; Roth club; row ex com; Russell club; Stanford crew; Stanford grotto; Stanford law association; Stanford relief fund; Stanford ski club; Stanford soccer association; Stanford village; Stern club; Stillman club; union club; union residence; WAA
  - ASSU Student Police Reports Sep. 1939-1943 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Student Police Reports 1945-50, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Student Police Reports 1950-55, 1950-1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Student Police Reports 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Student Police Reports 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Student Police Reports 1960-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Student Manager's Report, 1942-1943 (William R. Moran) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Student Manager's Report (George V. Denny III), 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Student Manager (J. Stephen Horn, Jr.), 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Report: Student Manager, Robert E. Gable, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Report: Student Financial Manager, William L. Tooley, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Report: Student Financial Manager, Larry J. Kelley, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Report of Student Financial Manager of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1963-64, Edward E. Shaw, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Treasurer, Series 4
  Records of the Treasurer include bound volumes of the Student Financial Managers' Reports 1955-1964, other reports, minutes, budgets, financial records, and other materials.
  - Annual funding agreement, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual funding agreement, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program Board funding appropriations, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Special fee assessment requests, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual funding agreement, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual funding agreement, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General fund allocations recommendations, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Discretionary funding applications for, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Discretionary funding applications, part 1 of 2, for, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Discretionary funding applications, part 2 of 2, for, 1985-86 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual funds, vol.1, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Annual funds, vol. 2, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Advance funding, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Program Board allocations, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Second discretionary cycle budgets Fall, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Funding agreements, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Program Board budget, 1987-88 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Third discretionary cycle budgets Winter, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Third discretionary cycle budgets Winter, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - First discretionary cycle budgets, 1988/89 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Second discretionary cycle budgets, 1988/89 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Program Board sixth discretionary, 1988/89 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Annual budget, 1988-89 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Annual budget, 1988-89 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SAIO Powpow annual funding, 1988-89 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Program Board fifth discretionary, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Program Board fifth discretionary, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Program Board annual funding, 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Discretionary cycle budget proposals, Winter Quarter, 1990/91 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Discretionary cycle budget proposals, Spring Quarter, 1990/91 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Annual budget proposals, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Program/Community Service Board recommendations, Fall, 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Funding practices, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Funding practices, 1985/86-1986/87 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous records, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Receipt for furniture, 10/23/87 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Receipts - office supplies (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Receipts - computer (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Price list (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ASSU price lists, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Journal transfers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Journal transfers, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - KZSU Budget, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Students' Phone Calls, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Budget, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Blue binder: Treasurer's Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Invoices / bank statements, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Program Board meeting notes (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Program Board information past (application, special fees, etc) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Pre-interview comments - Tracey Grey, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Students phone log, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Financial Manager's Correspondence, 1964-1965, Mar.-Dec. 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Financial Manager's Correspondence, Jan. 1964-Feb. 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Financial Manager's Correspondence, 1964 Mar -1965 Jun (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Financial Manager's Correspondence, 1965 Summer (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Financial Manager's Report, 1965 Summer (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stanford in Germany Groups XIII and XIV, Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stanford in Italy, Group X, Reports, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stanford in France, Group IV, Reports, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Quad Report, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Quad Reports, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Daily Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Daily Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Chaparral Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Sequoia Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Blotter Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Travel Service, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Speech Commission, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Ram's Head Productions (a), 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Ram's Head Productions (b), 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ram's Head Board, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cardinals Board, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Political Union Board, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Student Financial Manager's Report, Robert K. Best, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Washington University, Board of Student Affairs and Affiliated Student Organizations Annual Report, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Students' Organizations Fund for the Fiscal Year Ending August 31, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Students' Organizations Fund for the Fiscal Year Ending August 31, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Students' Organizations Fund for the Fiscal Year Ending August 31, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Report of the Students' Organizations Fund for the Fiscal Year Ending August 31, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Report: Student Financial Manager, Alfred S. Nelson, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Boat house Accounts, 1939-1954 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Union Operating Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Union Operating Statements, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Vending Machines, 1955-1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)